♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
HEY STAN, DID YOU SEE THAT
RAINBOW THIS MORNING?
YEAH,
IT WAS HUGE.
I HATE
THOSE THINGS!
NOBODY HATES
RAINBOWS.
YEAH, WHAT'S THERE
TO HATE ABOUT RAINBOWS?
WELL, YOU KNOW...
YOU'LL JUST BE SITTING THERE
MINDING YOUR OWN BUSINESS,
AND THEY'LL COME
MARCHING IN
AND CRAWL UP YOUR LEG
AND START BITING
THE INSIDE OF YOUR ASS.
AND YOU'LL BE ALL LIKE,
"HEY, GET OUT OF MY ASS,
YOU STUPID RAINBOWS!"
CARTMAN, WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING
ABOUT RAINBOWS.
I HATE THOSE
FREAKING THINGS.
RAINBOWS ARE THOSE
LITTLE ARCHES OF COLOR
THAT SHOW UP
DURING A RAINSTORM.
OH, RAIN BOWS!
OH YEAH, I LIKE THOSE,
THOSE ARE COOL.
WHAT WERE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
OH, NOTHING,
FORGET IT.
NO, WHAT MARCHES IN,
CRAWLS UP YOUR LEG
AND BITES THE INSIDE
OF YOUR ASS?!
NOTHING!
CHILDREN,
CHILDREN...
REMEMBER THE
"SAVE OUR FRAGILE PLANET"
ESSAY CONTEST
THAT YOU CHILDREN WORKED
SO HARD ON LAST MONTH?
ONE OF OUR VERY OWN
SOUTH PARK STUDENTS
HAS WON THE
NATIONAL PRIZE.
WOW, I KNEW
I WOULD WIN.
GOSH, MR. GARRISON,
THIS SURE IS EXCITING.
THAT'S RIGHT
MR. HAT,
THE WINNER OF THE NATIONAL
"SAVE OUR FRAGILE PLANET"
CONTEST IS...
ERIC CARTMAN.
WHAT?!
CONGRATULATIONS, ERIC,
ON WRITING THE
AWARD WINNING PAPER.
KICK ASS!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
HE DOESN'T KNOW A RAIN FOREST
FROM A POP-TART!
YEAH I DO,
POP-TARTS ARE FROSTED!
OUT OF OVER
A MILLION PAPERS
ERIC'S WAS CHOSEN AS
THE GRAND PRIZE WINNER.
WHAT DID YOU
WRITE ABOUT?
YOU KNOW,
THIS AND THAT.
HE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT HE WROTE ABOUT!
WHAT WAS YOUR PAPER
ABOUT, WENDY?
MY PAPER WAS ON
THE SUFFERING
OF BOTTLE-NOSED
DOLPHINS.
WELL,
YOU SEE?
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE WRITTEN
A PAPER ABOUT DOLPHINS.
DOLPHINS
ARE STUPID.
DUDE, DOLPHINS ARE THE SECOND
SMARTEST ANIMAL ON THE PLANET.
RIGHT.
IF THEY'RE
SO DAMN SMART
HOW COME THEY GET CAUGHT IN
FISHING NETS ALL THE TIME?
WHAT?!
WAIT, WAIT,
THERE'S MORE.
IT SAYS HERE
THAT ERIC'S TROPHY
WILL BE PRESENTED
TO HIM BY..
"KATHIE LEE GIFFORD"?
KATHIE LEE IS COMING
TO SOUTH PARK?
AND THE PRESENTATION WILL BE
ON NATIONAL TELEVISION.
TELEVISION?
( thinking )
Kathie Lee Gifford.
I don't believe it.
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
IN SOUTH PARK!
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS OUR CHANCE TO MAKE
A NAME FOR OURSELVES.
TO SHOW THAT WE'RE NOT
JUST SOME PISSANT
WHITE BREAD
MOUNTAIN TOWN.
BETTER YET, IT'S A CHANCE
FOR YOU TO GET SOME PUBLICITY.
YES!
IF I CAN SHOW HOW MUCH
I'VE TURNED SOUTH PARK AROUND,
I COULD BECOME
A SENATOR!
MAYBE EVEN
A STATE SENATOR!
MAYOR, WE SHOULD DECORATE
THE TOWN SQUARE.
THEN WE SHOULD HAVE THE CHEF
OF THE SCHOOL CAFETERIA
SING A SONG AND PLAY UP THE
ETHNIC DIVERSITY OF OUR TOWN.
THAT'S RIGHT!
HE'S A BLACK GUY,
ISN'T HE?
BLACK AS THE NIGHT
ITSELF, MAYOR.
YES!
AND WE CAN HAVE
THE CHILDREN OF SOUTH PARK
PUT ON A LITTLE PLAY.
KATHIE LEE
LOVES CHILDREN.
IF THEY'RE WORKING IN
A SWEATSHOP THAT IS.
OUCH!
THANK YOU.
YOU GUYS,
GUESS WHAT?
AFTER I'M ON TELEVISION,
I'M GONNA BE TOTALLY FAMOUS.
HITLER WAS
FAMOUS TOO.
HELLO THERE
CHILDREN.
HEY CHEF.
HOW ARE MY LITTLE
CRACKERS TODAY?
GOOD.
DID YOU HEAR
THE NEWS?
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
IS COMING TO SOUTH PARK!
YEAH, 'CAUSE
CARTMAN CHEATED
AND WON THE ENVIRONMENTAL
ESSAY CONTEST.
YEAH, YEAH,
WHATEVER.
BUT THE MAYOR
JUST CALLED
AND ASKED ME TO SING
AT THE CEREMONY.
WOW! ARE YOU
GONNA DO IT?
OF COURSE.
KATHIE LEE IS A BEAUTIFUL
SULTRY QUEEN
OF SEXUAL FANTASY.
AND IF
I SING TO HER...
MAYBE I CAN LURE HER INTO
A NIGHT OF EXOTIC DELECTATION.
YEAH THAT'D
BE COOL!
( mumbling )
WELL, THREE TIMES BIGGER
THAN FRANK GIFFORD'S ANYWAY.
I CAN'T EVEN CONCENTRATE
ON GRADING PAPERS
WITH ALL
THIS EXCITEMENT.
WHY YOU LOOKING AT ME
LIKE THAT, MR. HAT?
HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN ABOUT
ALL THE PAIN AND SUFFERING
THAT KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
CAUSED YOU?
MR. HAT,
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO
AND I WAS
ONLY A CHILD.
WE COULD'VE WON
THAT TALENT SHOW.
WE COULD'VE BEEN HUGE.
KNOCK KNOCK,
MR. HAT.
WHO'S THERE?
ORANGE.
ORANGE WHO?
ORANGE YOU GLAD
I DIDN'T SAY BANANA?
THANK YOU.
WELL MR. HAT,
LOOKS LIKE ME MIGHT WIN.
( announcer )
AND NOW OUR LAST
TALENT SHOW FINALIST,
KATHIE LEE EPSTEIN.
♪ IF THEY COULD SEE ME NOW,
THAT LITTLE GANG OF MINE ♪
♪ EATING FANCY CHOW
AND DRINKING FANCY WINE ♪
♪ I'D LIKE THOSE STUMBLE BUMS
TO SEE FOR A FACT ♪
♪ WHAT TYPE OF FIRST RATE,
TOP DRAWER CHUM I ATTRACT ♪
♪ ALL I CAN SAY IS "WOW",
LOOK AT WHERE I AM ♪
♪ TONIGHT I LANDED, POW
RIGHT IN A POT OF JAM ♪
♪ WHAT A SET UP, HOLY COW,
THEY'D NEVER BELIEVE IT ♪
♪ IF MY FRIENDS
COULD SEE ME NOW ♪
( applause )
IT WASN'T FAIR,
SHE HAD CHOREOGRAPHY.
HOW COULD WE
COMPETE WITH THAT?
BUT NOW SHE'S COMING
TO SOUTH PARK.
AND I KNOW A WAY
TO MAKE IT ALL BETTER.
HOW?
NO, MR. HAT!
I COULDN'T...
KILL KATHIE LEE GIFFORD.
MISS KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
WILL BE IN SOUTH PARK
TO PRESENT THE AWARD
TO SOME KID
FOR AN ESSAY.
THAT KID IS ME!
WHATEVER.
I'M GOING TO HAVE
YOU YOUNGSTERS
DO A PLAY ABOUT
THE HISTORY OF SOUTH PARK.
THAT'LL BE WONDERFUL,
WON'T IT, MR. HAT?
KILL HER!
MR. HAT!
MR. GARRISON,
I'M ASKING YOU TO
DIRECT OUR LITTLE PAY.
OH, THAT'S PERFECT.
YOU SEE MR. HAT,
WE DON'T HAVE TO KILL HER,
WE CAN JUST UPSTAGE HER.
MRS. MAYOR,
YOU MIGHT WANT TO
REVIEW THE ESSAYS.
WE THINK CARTMAN
MIGHT HAVE CHEATED.
WHO CARES?
NOW KIDS...
WHAT'S SAY WE GIVE IT
OUR SOUTH PARK BEST!
AND WHO'S OUR LITTLE
PRIZE WINNER AGAIN?
ME,
ERIC CARTMAN!
HOW ABOUT
WE GET IN SHAPE, HUH?
WE WANT TO LOOK OUR BEST
FOR THE TV CAMERAS, DON'T WE?
YES, MA'AM.
♪ I'M GONNA BE
ON TELEVISION ♪
WE DON'T BELIEVE
FOR A MINUTE
THAT YOU WON THAT CONTEST
FAIRLY, FAT BOY.
STOP DEFENDING
YOUR LITTLE GIRLFRIEND
FOR WRITING ABOUT
SOME STUPID FISH.
DUDE, DOLPHINS ARE
INTELLIGENT AND FRIENDLY.
INTELLIGENT
AND FRIENDLY
ON RYE BREAD
WITH SOME MAYONNAISE.
DOLPHINS ARE WAY
SMARTER THAN YOU.
IF THEY'RE SO SMART
WHY DO THEY LIVE IN IGLOOS?
DOLPHINS DON'T LIVE IN IGLOOS,
THAT'S ESKIMOS!
DOLPHINS, ESKIMOS,
WHO CARES?
IT'S ALL A BUNCH OF
TREE-HUGGING HIPPY CRAP.
TELL ME WHAT
YOU WROTE ABOUT!
I CAN'T.
I HAVE TO GO HOME
AND GET IN SHAPE!
YEAH, RIGHT!
YOU'LL GO SIT
IN FRONT OF THE TV
AND EAT CHEESY POOFS,
ASS-MASTER.
SCREW YOU,
HIPPY!
We'll be right back to
"Jesus and Pals" after this.
Do you need
to get in shape fast?
Wanna look your best?
Tired of the other guys
getting all the chicks?
Are you tired of being
a 90 pound weakling?
YEAH, I ONLY
WEIGH 90 POUNDS.
Then bulk up quick
with Weight Gain 4000!
YES!
Over 4,000 grams of
saturated fat per serving.
Its patented formula
is designed
to enter the mouth and
go directly to the stomach
where it is distributed
to the bloodstream!
Now available
at stores everywhere.
Get some today!
And say it with me...
Beefcake!
BEEFCAKE.
BEEFCAKE!
MOM, CAN YOU GET ME
SOME WEIGHT GAIN 4,000?
OKAY ERIC,
I'LL GET YOU
SOME TOMORROW.
BUT MOM,
I NEED IT FOR TOMORROW!
BUT TOMORROW
IS GROCERY DAY, ERIC.
MOM!
( squealing )
OKAY, OKAY.
WELL I GUESS I'LL BE GOING
TO THE STORE NOW THEN.
( dreaming )
♪ IF THEY COULD SEE ME NOW,
THAT LITTLE GANG OF MINE ♪
NO, NO!
KILL HER!
NO, MR. HAT,
I WON'T DO IT.
KILL!
THAT DOES IT.
YOU'RE GOING IN THE
DRESSER DRAWER, MR. HAT.
SHE'LL MAKE
A FOOL OF YOU AGAIN!
YOU CAN JUST STAY IN
THAT DRAWER, NEGATIVE NANCY.
HEY DUDES.
WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED THE THREE
FEET OF SNOW ON THE GROUND?
I HAVE A NICE BODY
AND I WANNA SHOW IT OFF!
YOU GOT THAT?
YOU'VE GOT TO WEIGH
90 POUNDS.
I'M UP TO 94,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
( mumbling )
YEAH THEY'RE ALMOST
AS BIG AS HIS MOMS!
LAUGH ALL YOU WANT!
I'M THE ONE WHO'S GONNA
BE ON TV LOOKING ALL BUFF.
WHAT'S THAT STUFF?
WEIGHT GAIN 4,000.
IT'S HELPING ME
BULK UP.
BULK UP TO WHAT?
FAT ASS?
SUPER FAT ASS?
HEY, I DON'T HAVE TO
TAKE THAT KIND OF CRAP
FROM YOU SCRAWNY
WEAKLINGS!
SWEET,
CHECK ME OUT.
I'M SUCH A BEEFCAKE I CAN'T EVEN
GET THROUGH THE DOOR.
C'MON PEOPLE, WE'VE GOT
TO TURN THIS PLACE AROUND!
HANG UP THE LIGHTS,
STRING UP UP THE BANNERS,
CASTRATE THE COWS!
WELL MR. GARRISON,
HOW IS THE
LITTLE PLAY GOING?
OH, FINE.
WE WERE JUST ABOUT
TO RUN IT FROM THE TOP.
OH, PLEASE DO.
I'M DYING
TO SEE IT.
ALL THE LITTLE PIONEERS
ON THIS SIDE OF THE STAGE.
GOOD.
AND ALL THE LITTLE INDIANS
GO TO THE CENTER OF THE STAGE.
AM I AN INDIAN
OR A PIONEER?
DO YOU HAVE A FEATHER
ON YOUR HEAD?
YES.
THEN YOU'RE
AN INDIAN.
OH.
OKAY, BABAY,
THIS IS YOUR LINE.
THIS IS THE STORY
OF SOUTH PARK.
IT BEGINS OVER
A HUNDRED YEARS AGO
WHEN THE NOBLE AND HEARTY
UTE INDIANS
LIVED ON THE LAND.
OH, DON'T THEY
LOOK ADORABLE?
THEN FROM THE EAST
CAME THE GREAT
WHITE PIONEERS.
( screaming )
OH, MY GOD!
THEY DID IT A LOT BETTER
THIS MORNING.
THEY HAD
MORE ENERGY.
THE PIONEERS MET
WITH THE INDIANS
AND NEGOTIATED
FOR THEIR FERTILE LANDS.
MR. GARRISON,
WE CANNOT HAVE OUR CHILDREN
BEATING EACH OTHER SENSELESS
IN FRONT OF
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD!
WELL WHAT
DO YOU WANT?
THIS IS HOW IT HAPPENED
IN THOSE DAYS.
TAKE THAT,
YOU STUPID INDIAN!
MR. GARRISON,
THIS IS NOT APPROPRIATE!
DO YOU
ACTUALLY THINK
THAT KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
WOULD ENJOY THIS?!
TO HELL WITH
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD!
( crowd gasping )
OH, MY GOD,
WHAT HAVE I SAID?
HE SAID "TO HELL WITH
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD"!
MR. GARRISON,
I AM DISMISSING YOU
FROM DIRECTING OUR PLAY.
IT HAPPENED AGAIN,
DIDN'T IT?
NOW WE DO THINGS
MY WAY.
I CAN'T KILL HER,
MR. HAT.
YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO DO IT.
( evil laugh )
WHOA, CARTMAN,
TALK ABOUT WIDE LOAD.
YEAH, I'M REALLY STARTING
TO FILL OUT NICELY.
YOU'RE NOT
FILLING OUT NICELY!
YOU'RE FATTER
THAN EVER!
I'M NOT FAT,
I'M GETTING IN SHAPE!
CARTMAN, YOU'RE SUCH
A FAT ASS
THEN WHEN YOU WALK DOWN
THE STREET PEOPLE GO,
"GODDAMNIT,
THAT'S A BIG FAT ASS!"
NO THEY DON'T,
YOU JEALOUS WEAKLING!
GODDAMN,
THAT'S A BIG FAT ASS!
HEY!
HI GUYS.
OH, LOOK,
ANOTHER HIPPY.
PEACE, WENDY.
SHUT UP,
CARTMAN!
♪ TWO LITTLE HIPPIES
SITTING IN A TREE ♪
I'M GONNA FIND
CARTMAN'S PAPER
AND GET TO
THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YES...
I NEED A GUN.
WOULD THIS BE FOR HUNTING,
OR PROTECTION,
OR OTHER?
OTHER.
ALRIGHTY THEN,
MAY I SUGGEST A
STRADFORD 12 MILLIMETER?
TRY IT ON!
THAT LOOKS
REALLY NICE ON YOU.
THE LACQUER BLACK
REALLY MATCHES YOUR EYES.
YOU TALKING TO ME?
ARE YOU TALKING
TO ME?
I DON'T KNOW,
IT'S A LITTLE SMALL.
OKAY...
HOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU TALKING TO ME?!
NO, I DON'T LIKE
THIS ONE EITHER.
HERE'S THE SAME GUN
WITH A WOOD FINISH.
YOU TALKING
TO ME?!
I DON'T SEE ANYBODY ELSE
AROUND HERE.
SO YOU MUST BE
TALKING TO ME.
I'LL TAKE IT.
HELLO?
"MY ESSAY,
BY ERIC CARTMAN."
"WHEN I WROTE
THE FOLLOWING PAGES,
"OR RATHER
THE BULK OF THEM,
I LIVED ALONE IN THE WOODS
ON THE SHORE OF..."
WELL, MR. HAT,
I GUESS OLD KATHIE LEE
REALLY WILL BE SURPRISED
WHEN SHE GETS
HERE TOMORROW.
SHE BEAT US IN THE TALENT SHOW
ALL THOSE YEARS AGO.
AND I THINK
WE OWE HER FOR THAT.
BA-BANG!
OH, MY GOD!
HOWDY, MR. GARRISON,
NICE GUN.
THANK YOU.
NICE GUN,
MR. GARRISON.
THANKS.
HELLO OFFICER
BARBRADY.
NICE GUN.
IS THERE
SOMEWHERE IN TOWN
WHERE I CAN GET
A GOOD CLEAR SHOT--
VIEW OF KATHIE LEE?
HMM, YOU KNOW
I THINK THE BOOK DEPOSITORY
WOULD BE A GOOD BET.
YES, THAT MIGHT
DO QUITE NICELY.
THANK YOU
OFFICER BARBRADY.
NO PROBLEM.
HA! CAUGHT YOU
RED-HANDED!
NO PICTURES
OF KATHIE LEE!
WHERE IS SHE?
THIS IS SWEET.
CAMERA CREWS
ARE SETTING UP.
AND I'M LOOKING
TOTALLY WHIPPED.
BEEFCAKE!
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE GONNA
GET ALL OF YOU IN FRAME.
YOU GUYS,
WE HAVE TO STOP HIM!
STOP WHO?
MR. GARRISON!
HE'S GOING TO TRY TO KILL
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD!
OH NO
YOU DON'T!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA RUIN
MY MOMENT OF FAME.
HE'S GOT A A GUN!
YOU GOTTA GET OVER
THIS WHOLE JEALOUSY THING.
SERIOUSLY,
JUST FACE IT.
I WROTE A BETTER PAPER
THAN YOU.
IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT I HAVE YOUR PAPER
AND I KNOW WHY YOU WON.
THERE'S SOMETHING MORE
IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW!
LET'S GO!
WENDY, YOU'VE GOT
TO PRIORITIZE.
WHAT'S MORE
IMPORTANT...
BEING ON TV OR SOME
STUPID ASSASSINATION?
STAN, I CAN'T
DO IT ALONE.
PLEASE?
( Kyle )
UH-OH, WE'RE LOSING HIM.
HERE SHE COMES!
( parade music )
DAMN, I GUESS I'M NOT
THE ONLY PERSON IN AMERICA
WHO'S THOUGHT OF KILLING
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD.
WE LOVE YOU,
KATHIE LEE!
( muffled )
I LOVE YOU TOO.
C'MON,
YOU LITTLE BITCH.
YOU'VE GOT TO COME OUT OF
YOUR PRECIOUS BUBBLE
SOONER OR LATER,
MISSY.
IT IS WITH GREAT
PRIDE AND HONOR
THAT I'D LIKE TO WELCOME
MRS. KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
TO SOUTH PARK!
( cheering )
AND NOW OUR VERY OWN
SOUTH PARK ELEMENTARY CHEF
WILL SING
A SPECIAL SONG
IN HONOR OF
MRS. LEE GIFFORD!
THANK YOU
MR. MAYOR.
YOU KNOW, KATHIE LEE,
YOU ARE A VERY SPECIAL WOMAN.
I DON'T MEAN SPECIAL
IN A MARY TYLER MOORE WAY
OR SPECIAL IN AN
EXTRA VALUE MEAL
AT "HAPPY BURGER" WAY...
NO, NO, NO,
I MEAN SPECIAL.
LIKE THE SONG OF
THE HUMMING BIRD
AS IT GETS READY TO FIND
THAT FEMALE HUMMING BIRD
AND MAKE SWEET LOVE TO IT
ALL NIGHT LONG.
JUST TWO HUMMING BIRDS
MOANING AND GROANING
AND LETTING
THEIR BODIES CARESS
AND TOUCH EACH OTHER
IN ECSTASY.
♪ OH KATHIE LEE ♪
♪ HOW I LOVE TO LAY
YOU DOWN ♪
♪ AND LICK EVERY INCH
OF YOUR BODY ♪
♪ WITH MY TONGUE ♪
WHAT!?
♪ KATHIE LEE,
YOU'RE MY SEXUAL FANTASY ♪
WHAT?!
♪ HOW ABOUT
YOU AND ME ♪
THANK YOU, CHEF,
FOR THAT HEART-WARMING SONG.
♪ MAKE SWEET LOVE ♪
THANK YOU, CHEF!
OH.
GOD BLESS YOU,
KATHIE LEE!
OFFICER BARBRADY,
MR. GARRISON IS ABOUT
TO KILL KATHIE LEE!
WE HAVE TO
FIND HIM!
WHAT? YOU MEAN
THE TEACHER?
WAIT A MINUTE...
IS THERE
SOMEWHERE IN TOWN
WHERE I CAN GET
A GOOD CLEAR SHOT--
VIEW OF KATHIE LEE?
I THINK THE BOOK DEPOSITORY
WOULD BE A GOOD BET.
BOOK DEPOSITORY.
DEPOSITORY.
DAMN, HE COULD
BE ANYWHERE!
I'LL SEND OUT
AN APB.
WENDY, LOOK!
AND NOW, HERE TO PRESENT
THE AWARD
FOR THE ENVIRONMENTAL ESSAY
TO OUR OWN ERIC KAUFMANN--
( Eric )
CARTMAN, GODDAMNIT!
IS YOUR FAVORITE CELEBRITY
AND MINE...
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD!
THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU ALL.
MR. GARRISON!
STOP!
LEAVE US.
WE MUST FINISH
WHAT WE HAVE BEGUN.
I KNOW THAT
SHE'S HURT YOU.
SHE'S HURT
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
YOU CAN'T KNOW.
YOU SHOULD'VE WON
THAT TALENT SHOW.
IT IS WITH GREAT HONOR
AND PRIDE
THAT I PRESENT THE WINNER
THIS TROPHY.
ERIC, WOULD YOU PLEASE
COME UP HERE.
HERE IT IS...
MY BIG MOMENT OF FAME.
AND THEN SHE FINISHED IT ALL
BY THROWING HER VOICE
WITH TWO DUMMIES
AT ONCE.
I KNOW THAT MR. GARRISON,
BUT THIS ISN'T THE ANSWER.
IT IS...
TOO LATE FOR ME,
YOUNG WENDY.
YOU SEE, I'VE LEARNED
SOMETHING TODAY.
YOU CAN'T WIN
ALL THE TIME.
AND IF YOU DON'T WIN,
YOU CERTAINLY CAN'T HOLD IT
AGAINST THE PERSON WHO DID
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
YOU EVER REALLY LOSE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GOOD.
MAN, DID SHE REALLY
THROW HER VOICE
WITH TWO DUMMIES
AT ONCE?
THE BITCH MUST DIE!
OH, MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY!
YOU BASTARD!
GUARD!
HEY COME BACK!
WE DIDN'T EVEN
GET TO DO OUR PLAY!
I GUESS THAT'S IT GUYS,
WRAP IT UP.
HEY WAIT A MINUTE!
WHEN DO I GET
TO BE ON TELEVISION?!
FORGET IT, KID.
NO KATHIE LEE,
NO PUBLIC INTEREST.
BUT I WON THE
ENVIRONMENTAL ESSAY CONTEST!
YOU DON'T DESERVE
TO WIN, CARTMAN,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
I'M HOLDING CARTMAN'S
AWARD-WINNING PAPER.
IT'S ACTUALLY NOTHING MORE
THAN "WALDEN"
WITH HENRY DAVID THOREAU'S
NAME CROSSED OUT
AND CARTMAN'S NAME
WRITTEN IN ITS PLACE.
WHO CARES?
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD'S
GONE!
WHAT ABOUT NOT
HOLDING ANYTHING
AGAINST THE PERSON
WHO WINS?
WELL, NOT IF
IT'S CARTMAN.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU
ALL GOING?!
THEY DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT "WALDEN" IS.
I BET IF "WALDEN" WAS A SITCOM
YOU'D ALL KNOW WHAT IT WAS!
C'MON, WENDY,
KYLE'S MOM WILL MAKE US
TUNA FISH SANDWICHES.
OH, WHAT THE HELL.
NO, NO!
NOW I'LL BE STUCK
IN THIS TOWN FOREVER
WITH ALL THESE STUPID HICK
RED-NECK, JOBLESS,
TRUCK DRIVING IDIOTS!
MAYOR,
THE MIC IS ON.
THOUGHT YOU COULD GET AWAY
WITH IT, MR. HAT?
I WOULD'VE GOTTEN
AWAY WITH IT
IF IT WEREN'T
FOR THOSE MEDDLING KIDS.
YOU'RE LUCKY YOU MISSED
KATHIE LEE GIFFORD
AND THAT
NOBODY GOT HURT.
WELL CHILDREN,
I'D LOVE TO,
BUT THE DOCTORS SAY THAT
MR. HAT NEEDS MORE THERAPY.
WE CAN STILL
GET HER!
I'M JUST SO SORRY THAT
I RUINED EVERYONE'S CHANCES
FOR BEING ON TV.
NOT CARTMAN, HE GETS
TO BE ON TV ANYWAY.
REALLY?
ON WHAT?
OBESITY...
ADIPOSITY...
CORPULENCE...
WHATEVER WORD YOU USE,
IT REPRESENTS ONE THING...
BEING A BIG FAT ASS.
WE HAVE WITH US TODAY,
LIVE VIA SATELLITE
ERIC CARTMAN
FROM SOUTH PARK,
WHO IS NOW SO OBESE
HE CAN'T EVEN GET
OUT OF HIS HOUSE.
WHEN IS THIS GONNA
BE ON THE AIR?
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU'D LIKE
TO SAY TO PEOPLE OUT THERE?
FOLLOW YOUR DREAMS!
YOU CAN REACH YOUR GOALS,
I'M LIVING PROOF.
BEEFCAKE,
BEEFCAKE!
HE NEEDS TO RUN HIS ASS
AROUND THE BLOCK A FEW TIMES.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE MORE
OF THAT GOOD LOVIN', CHEF?
DAMN, WOMAN!
I JUST GAVE YOU SWEET LOVIN'
FIVE MINUTES AGO!